{
    "subject": "resource/VMM-162",
    "predicate": "property/nickname",
    "object": "Golden Eagles",
    "human_readable": "The nickname of VMM-162 is 'Golden Eagles'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9231404066085815,
            "question": "How might the nickname 'Golden Eagles' influence the morale of VMM-162?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8385325074195862,
            "question": "What is the nickname of VMM-162?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7149542570114136,
            "question": "Is 'Golden Eagles' a nickname for a military unit?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.590035080909729,
            "question": "Are there any famous historical groups known as 'Golden Eagles'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4630984663963318,
            "question": "What could 'Golden Eagles' symbolize?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4239960312843323,
            "question": "What are some characteristics that eagles are known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3585704565048218,
            "question": "What type of unit is VMM-162?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.08841326832771301,
            "question": "Do you know any other military units with animal nicknames?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.08596967160701752,
            "question": "Can you think of other nicknames for military units?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.05923429876565933,
            "question": "Why might a military unit choose a nickname?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The nickname of VMM-162 is 'Golden Eagles'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4561_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you think of other nicknames for military units?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4561_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do you know any other military units with animal nicknames?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4561_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of unit is VMM-162?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4561_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4561_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4561_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4561_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4561_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4561_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4561_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4561_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4561_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4561_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4561_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents contain the following information:\n\n* VMM-162 is referred to as the \"Golden Eagles\" squadron. \n\nThis information supports the triple, so the answer is \"yes\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information clearly states that Marine Medium Tiltrotor Squadron 162 (VMM-162) has the nickname \"Golden Eagles\". Therefore, the statement \"The nickname of VMM-162 is 'Golden Eagles'\" is supported by the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}